<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>bneil.me</title><link>https://bneil.me/</link><description>Recent content on bneil.me</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>© bneil</copyright><lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 16:09:01 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://bneil.me/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>what-i-searched-today</title><link>https://bneil.me/posts/2023-11-02-what-i-searched-today/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 16:09:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bneil.me/posts/2023-11-02-what-i-searched-today/</guid><description>Today on domains I wish id bought sh.itjust.works buymea.beer Things ive researched that were non work related today Manifesting, is it bullshit? resulted in this article Had a recommendation from a friend to watch Mel Robbins: This One Hack Will Unlock Your Happier Life Was looking up minimalism techniques because I have clutter in the form of things I don&amp;rsquo;t need</description><webmention/></item><item><title>NaBloPoMo-maybe-going-to-try</title><link>https://bneil.me/posts/2023-11-02-nablopomo-maybe-going-to-try/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 16:04:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bneil.me/posts/2023-11-02-nablopomo-maybe-going-to-try/</guid><description>Saw this post and didn&amp;rsquo;t realize I was missing out on a writing challenge. So im going to try and come up with posts this month at a larger clip. So be prepared for some ideas that I can do on a daily basis.
One thing that usually detracts from these sorts of challenges is that its so hard to just submit work that isn&amp;rsquo;t &amp;lsquo;perfect&amp;rsquo;. That whole quest for perfectionalism is a tough one.</description><webmention/></item><item><title>weekly-writeup (week 4 of Oct 2023)</title><link>https://bneil.me/posts/2023-10-29-weekly-writeup/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2023 05:12:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bneil.me/posts/2023-10-29-weekly-writeup/</guid><description>Highlights had a bee try and take me out while picking up the kids lots of wins doing managerial tasks ended up watching a really great video by Amy Hupe got a few runs in! Takeaways Had a nice week that was largerly drawn out with meetings at work and a lots of journaling at home. Wasnt able to meet the daily meditations sessions I wanted, but did get in more running which was great.</description><webmention/></item><item><title>weekly-writeup (week 3 of Oct 2023)</title><link>https://bneil.me/posts/2023-10-22-weekly-writeup/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2023 19:24:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bneil.me/posts/2023-10-22-weekly-writeup/</guid><description>Highlights ordering some pizza late with the kids watching some blue jays chase off a squirell in the tree outside my office window hearing about the adventures at second and charles. turned out 20lbs of kids books was worth about a dollar a pound having some whiskey watching cycling youtube videos playing some pictionary games with coworkers Takeaways Was a really nice week out and I was able to take some advantage of it.</description><webmention/></item><item><title>To Fix or .. to wait</title><link>https://bneil.me/posts/2023-10-02-to-fix-or-wait/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2023 04:04:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bneil.me/posts/2023-10-02-to-fix-or-wait/</guid><description>Another day and another bug. It goes with the territory, and it can drive you up a wall. I know personally from having to watch production channels in slack slowly fill with issues that it can become a scheduling issue. When do we fix the issue? Whos impacted and why can&amp;rsquo;t we just spend one sprint without having to do a hotfix. So without further ado, ill unveil to you all the way I personally score issues that come flooding in.</description><webmention/></item><item><title>Hugo vs The AI</title><link>https://bneil.me/notes/2023-09-18-hugo-vs-the-ai/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 10:33:49 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://bneil.me/notes/2023-09-18-hugo-vs-the-ai/</guid><description>Hugo and AI Should be pretty easy, just toss a robots.txt into your static folder and toss the following into it
User-agent: GPTBot Disallow: / User-agent: ChatGPT-User Disallow: / User-agent: CCBot Disallow: /</description><webmention/></item><item><title>Atacama - A very very new social platform</title><link>https://bneil.me/posts/2023-09-15-2023-09-15-atacama-the-hidden-web/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 20:01:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bneil.me/posts/2023-09-15-2023-09-15-atacama-the-hidden-web/</guid><description>The hidden meetup Back in Febuary, I was going through some articles on social.coop a mastmastodon instance that describes itself as being A Fediverse instance for people interested in cooperative and collective projects.. As im likely to do, I have been slowly networking and checking out all the culture and discussions from the instance to self inform and make myself a slightly more informed netizen. The content on the site is especially resonating since I love cooperatives and have wanted to create a similar structure for myself and other developers in Colorado.</description><webmention/></item><item><title>Building CRUD with htmx</title><link>https://bneil.me/posts/2023-04-04-building-crud-with-htmx/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 04:23:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bneil.me/posts/2023-04-04-building-crud-with-htmx/</guid><description>The Stack (original) Going to use the following
frontend:
htmx backend:
golang / fiber for the language and server fig for configuration clover for the database The Repo Going to have a publicly hosted repo over at github.
Description of the project The project is just going to be a little pet project that I can experiment with. For fun and for this blog ill breakdown each of the development steps as I run into them.</description><webmention/></item><item><title>2023 January Wrap Up</title><link>https://bneil.me/posts/2023-02-02-2023-january-wrap-up/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 16:51:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bneil.me/posts/2023-02-02-2023-january-wrap-up/</guid><description>The month started great, a dry January. Which of course meant a few nightmare induced nights from not drinking. Which is crazy to me, as I usually have a beer and two shots and call it a night. All I can think is its sugar withdrawal or some such. Anyway, I love dry January since it gives me some time to feel what the absence of alcohol is like on a normal monday through friday.</description><webmention/></item><item><title>Testing Mermaid in Hugo</title><link>https://bneil.me/posts/2023-01-26-testing-mermaid-in-hugo/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 05:37:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bneil.me/posts/2023-01-26-testing-mermaid-in-hugo/</guid><description>This is a test of me adding mermaid.js to this blog
flowchart TB c1-->a2 subgraph one a1-->a2 end subgraph two b1-->b2 end subgraph three c1-->c2 end one --> two three --> two two --> c2</description><webmention/></item><item><title>Slipboxes and Evergreens</title><link>https://bneil.me/posts/2023-01-26-slipboxes-and-evergreens/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 05:03:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bneil.me/posts/2023-01-26-slipboxes-and-evergreens/</guid><description>For years ive struggled with keeping up with ideas. Growing them, expanding them and more importantly proving them out. Then, when coming to this website ive found it especially hard when it comes to figuring out what would be an interesting read. So I typically end up reading more on the subject of coming up with subjects. Wherein I found the holy grail and as others before me found this great strategy to ruminate on ideas.</description><webmention/></item><item><title>Books to Read 2023</title><link>https://bneil.me/posts/2023-01-25-books-to-read-2023/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 17:13:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bneil.me/posts/2023-01-25-books-to-read-2023/</guid><description>Fun and Fantasy NOFX: The Hepatitis Bathtub and Other Stories Personal Development second brain power of moments Shape Up https://basecamp.com/shapeup/0.3-chapter-01 the web of meaning the this Antifragile Stumbling on Happiness / Daniel Gilbert The Surrender Experiment / Michael Singer (better in audible) Way of the Superior Man / David Deida The Psychology of Money The Body Keeps The Score / Bessel van der Kolk the wisdom of in#security / Alan Watts Breaking the habit of being your self Recomendations wayward children series never let me go early riser outsiders babel daughter of the moon goddess empire of pain cormoran strike (the cuckoos calling) octavia butler (parable of the talents) the passage The one straw revolution Children of time Rich man sky a gentleman in moscow ( The Name of the Wind) The Kingkiller Chronicle (audiobook)</description><webmention/></item><item><title>Obsidian Plugins</title><link>https://bneil.me/posts/2022-12-14_obsidian-plugins/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 21:00:20 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://bneil.me/posts/2022-12-14_obsidian-plugins/</guid><description>Obsidian Plugins As an update Note Taking Apps I ended up biting the bullet and a now using obsidian sync. Just in terms of ease of mind. Totally worth the investment.
So with that my current list is as follows
[ &amp;#34;table-editor-obsidian&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;templater-obsidian&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;dataview&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;cm-editor-syntax-highlight-obsidian&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;obsidian-minimal-settings&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;obsidian-kanban&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;periodic-notes&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;workbench-obsidian&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;readwise-official&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;quickadd&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;obsidian-excel-to-markdown-table&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;obsidian-outliner&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;obsidian-projects&amp;#34; ]</description><webmention/></item><item><title>Klara and the sun</title><link>https://bneil.me/review/books/klara/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 22:45:53 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://bneil.me/review/books/klara/</guid><description>The way this book introduces its world is fantastic. It was a slow reveal behind the eyes of an artificial friend named Klara. Whose innocence and observations creates a truly delightful narrative. We start with Klara inside a store waiting to be purchased and interacting with other artificial friends. What struck me first just the genuine curiosity that Klara showed towards her world and how that was a rarity in her kind.</description><webmention/></item><item><title>Webmentions are fun</title><link>https://bneil.me/posts/2021-07-29-webmentions-are-fun/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 11:39:43 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://bneil.me/posts/2021-07-29-webmentions-are-fun/</guid><description>On Implementing webmentions When going through the process of implementing webmentions I found the process to be a little challenging. However, I would imagine most of my issues were due to having a static site. Lucking, I found some really excellent examples of people who had set things up and also used hugo!
So for those looking to for some help, I found kaushalmodi and also integrating-webmentions-into-hugo to have an excellent partial to follow.</description><webmention/></item><item><title>The Only Good Indians</title><link>https://bneil.me/review/books/good_indians/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jan 2022 22:45:53 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://bneil.me/review/books/good_indians/</guid><description>This was a quick read and a really great horror story. It followed four native americans who had done some unspeakable evil to a group of elk late into their teens. The Elk they took down had memories and from them spawned something awful id rather not talk about.</description><webmention/></item><item><title>How Rory Thorne Destroyed the Multiverse</title><link>https://bneil.me/review/books/rory/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 22:45:53 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://bneil.me/review/books/rory/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m a sucker for good dialogue. Thankfully this book delivers that in bountiful helpings.
Whether it&amp;rsquo;s a fairies gift or the divine. very human. multiverse to which we are introduced. The plot is one that is easy to imagine and easy to fall into. Enter Rory Thorne. First woman born to the house Thorne in 200 years. Not weird at all, right? Well, that&amp;rsquo;s what you get for not paying attention.</description><webmention/></item><item><title>Piranesi</title><link>https://bneil.me/review/books/paranesi/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 22:45:53 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://bneil.me/review/books/paranesi/</guid><description>Really weird but really neat book. A book in which the protagonist and environment, were constant highlights. The supernatural gift of navigating the maze of rooms, makes Piranesi a delight. Fugue state aside. The internal monologue. Peaceful descriptions and endless ocean waves. Put me in a mood that I hadn&amp;rsquo;t felt since I was younger. Listening to the ocean ebb and flow. crash and dance.
Couldn&amp;rsquo;t recommend this book enough. Even the ending pages were spellbinding.</description><webmention/></item><item><title>Books Read in 2022</title><link>https://bneil.me/posts/books_2022/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 22:45:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bneil.me/posts/books_2022/</guid><description>Selfhelp Book - Atomic Habits Book - Little Habits Book -Designing Your Life Book - Willpower Book - Obfuscation Book - Thinking fast and slow] second brain power of moments Shape Up https://basecamp.com/shapeup/0.3-chapter-01 the web of meaning Fun and Fantasy [[Book - Child of fire]] Recomended The invisible life of addie la rue The shadow of the wind The Knife of Never Letting Go klara and the sun never let me go</description><webmention/></item><item><title>Babylon's Ashes</title><link>https://bneil.me/review/books/babylons_ashes/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Oct 2021 13:48:53 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://bneil.me/review/books/babylons_ashes/</guid><description>Legacies and Strategies The free navy. Finally given some room to govern, falls. It was a wonderful exposition into how a careful story. Well crafted. Can create a narrative that can form and hold an empire. That and rail guns keeping your main foothold to said empire in check.
Bablyon&amp;rsquo;s ashes was a fantastic addition to the expanse series. It was a page turner. A beautiful tale of megalomania and revenge.</description><webmention/></item><item><title>First Post</title><link>https://bneil.me/posts/first_post/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Oct 2021 13:27:13 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://bneil.me/posts/first_post/</guid><description>Trying to follow along and get a build for hugo and for gemini working in github actions.
nice</description><webmention/></item><item><title>Nemesis Games</title><link>https://bneil.me/review/books/nemesis_games/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2021 13:48:53 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://bneil.me/review/books/nemesis_games/</guid><description>Never break the party It&amp;rsquo;s been really interesting in other expanse novels, the close releationships. The comradery. Then here, you see people. People that want to reconnect.
It was, at this point, my investiment into the crew of the Rocinate was tested. I didn&amp;rsquo;t want these characters to leave. To explore their own backstories. But they did.
Then rocks fell and all shit went haywire. It was glorius.
Naomi&amp;rsquo;s character ark in particular was so spectacular that I had on occasion just had to stop gushing.</description><webmention/></item><item><title>Cibola Burn</title><link>https://bneil.me/review/books/cibola_burn/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2021 13:48:53 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://bneil.me/review/books/cibola_burn/</guid><description>He reaches out Sometimes I read a book and I start laughing at just how bad things keep getting regardless of the beste intentions of the characters in the book. Having now gone through a few of these expanse books, I knew that the crew of the Rocinante, were going to see wild things in the through the gates. But I couldn&amp;rsquo;t even imagine how entertaining the middle of this book would be.</description><webmention/></item><item><title>Abaddons Gate</title><link>https://bneil.me/review/books/abaddons_gate/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 19:22:33 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://bneil.me/review/books/abaddons_gate/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m burning through these books and this one was no different.
Maybe it&amp;rsquo;s the instant draw.
To characters whose only hope of kindling a romantic hookup is belting themselves into a junker spaceship and hurling themselves through a gate built from the reconstituted remains of Venus.
But damn.
The flair seems so human, I could see it being real.
Abaddon&amp;rsquo;s Gate centers around the aforementioned ring. It&amp;rsquo;s existence bringing the whole of humanity towards it.</description><webmention/></item><item><title>test</title><link>https://bneil.me/mentions/test/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 19:22:33 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://bneil.me/mentions/test/</guid><description>What an amazing article, wtg.</description><webmention>
https://bneil.me/notes/note_connecting_to_rds/</webmention></item><item><title>Calibans War</title><link>https://bneil.me/review/books/calibans_war/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jun 2021 10:33:49 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://bneil.me/review/books/calibans_war/</guid><description>I couldn&amp;rsquo;t put this title down from page one. Where in Leviathans Wake I was impressed by the world building and just wild adventure, in caliban&amp;rsquo;s war the character and story arcs are on a completely different level. From a war breaking out in the solar systems only bread basket too running full throttle towards a space mutant and even a kidnapping - I was absolutely delighted.
All while introducing characters like Avasarala, a head strong - tactical politician boss bitch archetype and Bobby a gunnery sergeant who&amp;rsquo;s mental health is threatened very early in the book.</description><webmention/></item><item><title>Leviathan Wakes</title><link>https://bneil.me/review/books/leviathan_wakes/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jun 2021 10:33:49 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://bneil.me/review/books/leviathan_wakes/</guid><description>Really great world building, interesting plot and just enough tension to really feel like an adventure. I was a little confused when reading this book at first since the prologue was really odd. That and the whiplash we get as we are first getting introduced into the world that James Corey paints for us.
For me my favorite character was Miller, and I was enjoying the tug of what felt like two protagonists in a single story.</description><webmention/></item><item><title>Connecting/Migrations in RDS</title><link>https://bneil.me/notes/note_connecting_to_rds/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 17:03:50 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://bneil.me/notes/note_connecting_to_rds/</guid><description>Goose Since goose uses pq under the hood, to hit remote urls
goose postgres &amp;#34;user=postgres password=${PROD_PGPASS} dbname=test sslmode=disable host=database.rds.amazonaws.com&amp;#34; status PSQL / RDS I didnt have a default database created, so I needed to psql into it - summoning psql via docker container
docker run -it --rm jbergknoff/postgresql-client postgresql://postgres:${PROD_PGPASS}@database.rds.amazonaws.com:5432</description><webmention/></item><item><title>Note taking apps</title><link>https://bneil.me/posts/2021-05-28_note-taking-apps/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 May 2021 18:13:24 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://bneil.me/posts/2021-05-28_note-taking-apps/</guid><description>Obsidian Currently Using
Notes/Second Brain obsidian.md -&amp;gt; sourcehut -&amp;gt; all mobile devices</description><webmention/></item><item><title>Audit Service - RDS</title><link>https://bneil.me/posts/2021-05-28_rds-audit-service/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 May 2021 11:39:43 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://bneil.me/posts/2021-05-28_rds-audit-service/</guid><description>Audit Service or Round 2 Fight Description When I started to think more critically about how interactions would work inside dynamodb for auditing I quickly learned about pain. Lots and lots of pain. Including the fact id probably end up having to use dynamodb streams and couple that with elasticsearch. So im not going to even entertain that idea and am going down the ol trusty sql route.
Creating the database Im still on an older version of terraform, so public shamming for being on 0.</description><webmention/></item><item><title>Audit Service - Dynamodb</title><link>https://bneil.me/posts/audit-dynamodb/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 May 2021 11:13:53 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://bneil.me/posts/audit-dynamodb/</guid><description>Audit Service Description Decided that I wanted an audit db and service to help keep track of user behaviors. Since I already have some in Redis, and some in Postgres I thought this might be a useful exercise. The main thing id like to accomplish with this code is going to be a way to track events and break them down by week/month/year per user and per company.
Im having some self debate about creating tables for the tallies or if I should just be creating them on the fly using a query.</description><webmention/></item><item><title>Dynamo DB Pages</title><link>https://bneil.me/notes/dynamodb_pages/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2021 10:33:49 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://bneil.me/notes/dynamodb_pages/</guid><description>Dynamo code snippet Recently got burned because we needed to do a recursive paging through dynamo
var listOfThings []Whatever err := store.ScanPages(input, func (page *dynamodb.ScanOutput, lastPage bool) bool { for _, item := range page.Items { var whateva Whatever if val, ok := item[&amp;#34;jval&amp;#34;]; ok { err := json.Unmarshal([]byte(*val.S), &amp;amp;whateva) if err != nil { return true // its like continue } listOfThings = append(listOfThings, whateva) } } return !lastPage }) if err !</description><webmention/></item><item><title>Replaying No Mans Sky</title><link>https://bneil.me/posts/replaying-nms/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2021 10:33:49 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://bneil.me/posts/replaying-nms/</guid><description>No Man Sky Used to play the game a few years back and am starting to get back into it.
Whats Great Been really enjoying getting back into the game. After a few hours I even got to see a sand worm comes flying out of the ground. I was so used to just being bored going from world to procedurally generated world that it shook me for a second.</description><webmention/></item><item><title>Using MFA with AWS CLI</title><link>https://bneil.me/notes/2021-05-06-mfa-aws/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 May 2021 12:24:40 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://bneil.me/notes/2021-05-06-mfa-aws/</guid><description>MFA on AWS Cli Description Just writing down the steps ive been manually taken for updating my credentials to use ecr in aws from the cli.
Check authy on phone and write down code Check arn from aws and write that down Issue this command aws sts get-session-token --serial-number &amp;lt;arn here&amp;gt; --token-code &amp;lt;authy code&amp;gt; Take those values and plop the into ~/.aws/credentials Ensure the profile is [mfa] Convert the json to the toml keys &amp;ldquo;SecretAccessKey&amp;rdquo;: aws_secret_access_key &amp;ldquo;SessionToken&amp;rdquo;: aws_session_token &amp;ldquo;AccessKeyId&amp;rdquo;: aws_access_key_id Issue the command aws ecr get-login --profile mfa ecr above can be replaced with any service</description><webmention/></item><item><title>Nextjs Crud :: Setup</title><link>https://bneil.me/posts/2021-04-21-nextjs-crud/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 20:06:34 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://bneil.me/posts/2021-04-21-nextjs-crud/</guid><description>Setup So the gist of the below is that we are creating a starter nextjs application, typescript, converting to yarn and finally installing both tailwind css and tailwind jit.
λ&amp;gt; npx create-next-app nextjs-crud --use-npm --example &amp;#34;https://github.com/vercel/next-learn-starter/tree/master/learn-starter&amp;#34; λ&amp;gt; cd nextjs-crud λ&amp;gt; touch tsconfig.json λ&amp;gt; npm install --save-dev typescript @types/react λ&amp;gt; rm -f package-lock.json λ&amp;gt; yarn add -d tailwindcss@latest postcss@latest autoprefixer@latest λ&amp;gt; npx tailwindcss init -p λ&amp;gt; yarn add @tailwindcss/jit tailwindcss postcss if you want to learn more about the &amp;lsquo;why&amp;rsquo; you should use the jit instead of using tailwind directly,</description><webmention/></item><item><title>Migrating to Dynamo</title><link>https://bneil.me/posts/2021-04-20-dynamo_struct/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 10:15:26 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://bneil.me/posts/2021-04-20-dynamo_struct/</guid><description>Another store getting migrated Today&amp;rsquo;s pivotal tasks are all related towards moving things away from redis and into dynamo. So far ive gotten the underpinnings done by creating a dynamo store
The main struct looks like this
type DynamoStore struct { tableName string primaryKey string store *dynamodb.DynamoDB } The funny thing is that im basically treating dynamo in the same way I was treating redis. Which is as primarily a key value store.</description><webmention/></item><item><title>On Notes</title><link>https://bneil.me/notes/2021-04-19-taking-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Apr 2021 16:27:57 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://bneil.me/notes/2021-04-19-taking-notes/</guid><description>Hugo for note taking I&amp;rsquo;m wondering if using Hugo for writing notes would even be applicable to my current work flows. Right now I usually just use Evernote, but then I never really go into Evernote and re-review all the things ive noted.
I keep feeling like there has to be a way to manage GTD, alongside tools that im working with daily because seriously, the amount of context switching in terms of apps/sites to plan any one project seems crazy.</description><webmention/></item><item><title>WASM and Webmentions</title><link>https://bneil.me/posts/wasm/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2021 15:36:52 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://bneil.me/posts/wasm/</guid><description>Webmentions So as I journey through the fun webmentions, it looks like since im just using github pages, I would migrate over to using cloudflare so I could play more with webworkers. My last attempt was that Danny Devito Quote generator that I believe was working fairly well.
Although, having said that it really isnt at the point id like it to be. I originally wanted an &amp;ldquo;always sunny in philadelphia&amp;rdquo; to regale my coworkers with.</description><webmention/></item><item><title>Not dead</title><link>https://bneil.me/posts/awake/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Apr 2021 11:23:39 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://bneil.me/posts/awake/</guid><description>Whats going on? It all started with finding a webring. I hadnt seen one since the mid 90&amp;rsquo;s and the accidental stumbling upon one was almost magical. If you&amp;rsquo;ve never had the pleasure, a web ring was this piece of tech that was largely social. It was a way of finding genres of websites you were interested in and daisy chaining between them. Largely this was before google owned search and the &amp;rsquo;little&amp;rsquo; guys like alta vista were king.</description><webmention/></item><item><title>About Me</title><link>https://bneil.me/about/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bneil.me/about/</guid><description>My name is Ben Neil, a polyglot engineer. I have had the privilege to work the past eleven years making websites, services, documentation and tools for amazing companies.
I&amp;rsquo;m obsessed with technology and programming - mainy linux, hypervisors, containers, unikernels, scala, rust, go etc. Ive got a real problem researching tools and enjoy writing then rewriting internal documentation.
Publications Recently (well in 2016) I co-authored a book called Professional Scala, it was an exciting experience and I really enjoyed the feedback from the scala community.</description><webmention/></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>https://bneil.me/contact/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bneil.me/contact/</guid><description>Have questions or want to discuss programming?
if you have keybase you can follow me and im usually on the messaging app reach out on Twitter</description><webmention/></item><item><title>Resume</title><link>https://bneil.me/resume/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bneil.me/resume/</guid><description>Technical Overview I really use a lot of tech soup - so these change all the time
Docker EE and Kubernetes Go, Rust, Scala and more Drone, Jenkins and Gitlab PostgreSQL, MySQL, Redis and more Vue.js, next.js Experience Compliable CTO Co-Founder Sept 2020 to Present
Same role just now with a new name!
Technical Toolset Docker, Aws Stack, Go
REBRIC Chief Technical Officer Nov 2016 to Sept 2020 Lead the long-term technical strategy development and tactical execution of those strategies at Rebric Directed technical teams and resources in solutions for design, development and delivery services to benefit the buisness Developed a road map to optimize the rollout of the Rebric infrastructure Launched development, testing and production environments for all Rebric infrastructure Articulated a clear vision, to drive technical discussions throughout the SDLC lifecycle to be in parity with the buisness Technical Toolset Docker, Jenkins, Ambassador, Play, Rust, Go Microservices, OpenFaas, GCP, AWS.</description><webmention/></item><item><title>now</title><link>https://bneil.me/now/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bneil.me/now/</guid><description>Last Updated: Nov 2, 2023
As of right now, its the start of November, looking forward to a fun filled month of CTO&amp;rsquo;n and getting ready for some friends and family at Thanksgiving time. I really love this month for giving a more focused opportunity to remember to show thanks for friends and family. Since, I know that I can get a really into my own problems and worlds.
Reading A sanderson book Listening To Podcasts - mostly &amp;lsquo;if books could kill&amp;rsquo; So many more.</description><webmention/></item><item><title>Nondistributable Artifacts</title><link>https://bneil.me/posts/docker-nondistributable-artifacts/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bneil.me/posts/docker-nondistributable-artifacts/</guid><description>The Mystery I was reading through the docker documentation for docker registry and ran into this curious idea of nondistributable artifacts and how that related to some layers that are proprietary. Which got me thinking about how I could setup my own non distributable layers.
So looking into microsoft/windowsservercore I figured since those had some foreign layers I could take a gander at what was in the manifest which made particular layers &amp;ldquo;foreign&amp;rdquo;.</description><webmention/></item></channel></rss>