<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>bneil.me</title><link>https://bneil.me/</link><description>Recent content on bneil.me</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>© bneil</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Oct 2021 13:48:53 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://bneil.me/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Babylon's Ashes</title><link>https://bneil.me/review/books/babylons_ashes/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Oct 2021 13:48:53 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://bneil.me/review/books/babylons_ashes/</guid><description>Legacies and Strategies The free navy. Finally given some room to govern, falls. It was a wonderful exposition into how a careful story. Well crafted. Can create a narrative that can form and hold an empire. That and rail guns keeping your main foothold to said empire in check.
Bablyon&amp;rsquo;s ashes was a fantastic addition to the expanse series. It was a page turner. A beautiful tale of megalomania and revenge.</description></item><item><title>First Post</title><link>https://bneil.me/posts/first_post/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Oct 2021 13:27:13 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://bneil.me/posts/first_post/</guid><description>Trying to follow along and get a build for hugo and for gemini working in github actions.
nice</description></item><item><title>Nemesis Games</title><link>https://bneil.me/review/books/nemesis_games/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2021 13:48:53 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://bneil.me/review/books/nemesis_games/</guid><description>Never break the party It&amp;rsquo;s been really interesting in other expanse novels, the close releationships. The comradery. Then here, you see people. People that want to reconnect.
It was, at this point, my investiment into the crew of the Rocinate was tested. I didn&amp;rsquo;t want these characters to leave. To explore their own backstories. But they did.
Then rocks fell and all shit went haywire. It was glorius.
Naomi&amp;rsquo;s character ark in particular was so spectacular that I had on occasion just had to stop gushing.</description></item><item><title>Cibola Burn</title><link>https://bneil.me/review/books/cibola_burn/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2021 13:48:53 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://bneil.me/review/books/cibola_burn/</guid><description>He reaches out Sometimes I read a book and I start laughing at just how bad things keep getting regardless of the beste intentions of the characters in the book. Having now gone through a few of these expanse books, I knew that the crew of the Rocinante, were going to see wild things in the through the gates. But I couldn&amp;rsquo;t even imagine how entertaining the middle of this book would be.</description></item><item><title>Abaddons Gate</title><link>https://bneil.me/review/books/abaddons_gate/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 19:22:33 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://bneil.me/review/books/abaddons_gate/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m burning through these books and this one was no different.
Maybe it&amp;rsquo;s the instant draw.
To characters whose only hope of kindling a romantic hookup is belting themselves into a junker spaceship and hurling themselves through a gate built from the reconstituted remains of Venus.
But damn.
The flair seems so human, I could see it being real.
Abaddon&amp;rsquo;s Gate centers around the aforementioned ring. It&amp;rsquo;s existence bringing the whole of humanity towards it.</description></item><item><title>Calibans War</title><link>https://bneil.me/review/books/calibans_war/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jun 2021 10:33:49 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://bneil.me/review/books/calibans_war/</guid><description>I couldn&amp;rsquo;t put this title down from page one. Where in Leviathans Wake I was impressed by the world building and just wild adventure, in caliban&amp;rsquo;s war the character and story arcs are on a completely different level. From a war breaking out in the solar systems only bread basket too running full throttle towards a space mutant and even a kidnapping - I was absolutely delighted.
All while introducing characters like Avasarala, a head strong - tactical politician boss bitch archetype and Bobby a gunnery sergeant who&amp;rsquo;s mental health is threatened very early in the book.</description></item><item><title>Leviathan Wakes</title><link>https://bneil.me/review/books/leviathan_wakes/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jun 2021 10:33:49 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://bneil.me/review/books/leviathan_wakes/</guid><description>Really great world building, interesting plot and just enough tension to really feel like an adventure. I was a little confused when reading this book at first since the prologue was really odd. That and the whiplash we get as we are first getting introduced into the world that James Corey paints for us.
For me my favorite character was Miller, and I was enjoying the tug of what felt like two protagonists in a single story.</description></item><item><title>Connecting/Migrations in RDS</title><link>https://bneil.me/notes/note_connecting_to_rds/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 17:03:50 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://bneil.me/notes/note_connecting_to_rds/</guid><description>Goose Since goose uses pq under the hood, to hit remote urls
goose postgres &amp;#34;user=postgres password=${PROD_PGPASS} dbname=test sslmode=disable host=database.rds.amazonaws.com&amp;#34; status PSQL / RDS I didnt have a default database created, so I needed to psql into it - summoning psql via docker container
docker run -it --rm jbergknoff/postgresql-client postgresql://postgres:${PROD_PGPASS}@database.rds.amazonaws.com:5432</description></item><item><title>Note taking apps</title><link>https://bneil.me/posts/2021-05-28_note-taking-apps/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 May 2021 18:13:24 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://bneil.me/posts/2021-05-28_note-taking-apps/</guid><description>Obsidian Currently Using
Notes/Second Brain obsidian.md -&amp;gt; sourcehut -&amp;gt; all mobile devices</description></item><item><title>Audit Service - RDS</title><link>https://bneil.me/posts/2021-05-28_rds-audit-service/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 May 2021 11:39:43 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://bneil.me/posts/2021-05-28_rds-audit-service/</guid><description>Audit Service or Round 2 Fight Description When I started to think more critically about how interactions would work inside dynamodb for auditing I quickly learned about pain. Lots and lots of pain. Including the fact id probably end up having to use dynamodb streams and couple that with elasticsearch. So im not going to even entertain that idea and am going down the ol trusty sql route.
Creating the database Im still on an older version of terraform, so public shamming for being on 0.</description></item><item><title>Audit Service - Dynamodb</title><link>https://bneil.me/posts/audit-dynamodb/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 May 2021 11:13:53 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://bneil.me/posts/audit-dynamodb/</guid><description>Audit Service Description Decided that I wanted an audit db and service to help keep track of user behaviors. Since I already have some in Redis, and some in Postgres I thought this might be a useful exercise. The main thing id like to accomplish with this code is going to be a way to track events and break them down by week/month/year per user and per company.
Im having some self debate about creating tables for the tallies or if I should just be creating them on the fly using a query.</description></item><item><title>Dynamo DB Pages</title><link>https://bneil.me/notes/dynamodb_pages/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2021 10:33:49 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://bneil.me/notes/dynamodb_pages/</guid><description>Dynamo code snippet Recently got burned because we needed to do a recursive paging through dynamo
var listOfThings []Whatever err := store.ScanPages(input, func (page *dynamodb.ScanOutput, lastPage bool) bool { for _, item := range page.Items { var whateva Whatever if val, ok := item[&amp;#34;jval&amp;#34;]; ok { err := json.Unmarshal([]byte(*val.S), &amp;amp;whateva) if err != nil { return true // its like continue } listOfThings = append(listOfThings, whateva) } } return !</description></item><item><title>Replaying No Mans Sky</title><link>https://bneil.me/posts/replaying-nms/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2021 10:33:49 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://bneil.me/posts/replaying-nms/</guid><description>No Man Sky Used to play the game a few years back and am starting to get back into it.
Whats Great Been really enjoying getting back into the game. After a few hours I even got to see a sand worm comes flying out of the ground. I was so used to just being bored going from world to procedurally generated world that it shook me for a second.</description></item><item><title>Using MFA with AWS CLI</title><link>https://bneil.me/notes/2021-05-06-mfa-aws/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 May 2021 12:24:40 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://bneil.me/notes/2021-05-06-mfa-aws/</guid><description>MFA on AWS Cli Description Just writing down the steps ive been manually taken for updating my credentials to use ecr in aws from the cli.
Check authy on phone and write down code Check arn from aws and write that down Issue this command aws sts get-session-token --serial-number &amp;lt;arn here&amp;gt; --token-code &amp;lt;authy code&amp;gt; Take those values and plop the into ~/.aws/credentials Ensure the profile is [mfa] Convert the json to the toml keys &amp;ldquo;SecretAccessKey&amp;rdquo;: aws_secret_access_key &amp;ldquo;SessionToken&amp;rdquo;: aws_session_token &amp;ldquo;AccessKeyId&amp;rdquo;: aws_access_key_id Issue the command aws ecr get-login --profile mfa ecr above can be replaced with any service</description></item><item><title>Nextjs Crud :: Setup</title><link>https://bneil.me/posts/2021-04-21-nextjs-crud/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 20:06:34 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://bneil.me/posts/2021-04-21-nextjs-crud/</guid><description>Setup So the gist of the below is that we are creating a starter nextjs application, typescript, converting to yarn and finally installing both tailwind css and tailwind jit.
λ&amp;gt; npx create-next-app nextjs-crud --use-npm --example &amp;#34;https://github.com/vercel/next-learn-starter/tree/master/learn-starter&amp;#34; λ&amp;gt; cd nextjs-crud λ&amp;gt; touch tsconfig.json λ&amp;gt; npm install --save-dev typescript @types/react λ&amp;gt; rm -f package-lock.json λ&amp;gt; yarn add -d tailwindcss@latest postcss@latest autoprefixer@latest λ&amp;gt; npx tailwindcss init -p λ&amp;gt; yarn add @tailwindcss/jit tailwindcss postcss if you want to learn more about the &amp;lsquo;why&amp;rsquo; you should use the jit instead of using tailwind directly,</description></item><item><title>Migrating to Dynamo</title><link>https://bneil.me/posts/2021-04-20-dynamo_struct/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 10:15:26 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://bneil.me/posts/2021-04-20-dynamo_struct/</guid><description>Another store getting migrated Today&amp;rsquo;s pivotal tasks are all related towards moving things away from redis and into dynamo. So far ive gotten the underpinnings done by creating a dynamo store
The main struct looks like this
type DynamoStore struct { tableName string primaryKey string store *dynamodb.DynamoDB } The funny thing is that im basically treating dynamo in the same way I was treating redis. Which is as primarily a key value store.</description></item><item><title>On Notes</title><link>https://bneil.me/notes/2021-04-19-taking-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Apr 2021 16:27:57 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://bneil.me/notes/2021-04-19-taking-notes/</guid><description>Hugo for note taking I&amp;rsquo;m wondering if using Hugo for writing notes would even be applicable to my current work flows. Right now I usually just use Evernote, but then I never really go into Evernote and re-review all the things ive noted.
I keep feeling like there has to be a way to manage GTD, alongside tools that im working with daily because seriously, the amount of context switching in terms of apps/sites to plan any one project seems crazy.</description></item><item><title>WASM and Webmentions</title><link>https://bneil.me/posts/wasm/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2021 15:36:52 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://bneil.me/posts/wasm/</guid><description>Webmentions So as I journey through the fun webmentions, it looks like since im just using github pages, I would migrate over to using cloudflare so I could play more with webworkers. My last attempt was that Danny Devito Quote generator that I believe was working fairly well.
Although, having said that it really isnt at the point id like it to be. I originally wanted an &amp;ldquo;always sunny in philadelphia&amp;rdquo; to regale my coworkers with.</description></item><item><title>Not dead</title><link>https://bneil.me/posts/awake/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Apr 2021 11:23:39 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://bneil.me/posts/awake/</guid><description>Whats going on? It all started with finding a webring. I hadnt seen one since the mid 90&amp;rsquo;s and the accidental stumbling upon one was almost magical. If you&amp;rsquo;ve never had the pleasure, a web ring was this piece of tech that was largely social. It was a way of finding genres of websites you were interested in and daisy chaining between them. Largely this was before google owned search and the &amp;lsquo;little&amp;rsquo; guys like alta vista were king.</description></item><item><title>About Me</title><link>https://bneil.me/about/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bneil.me/about/</guid><description>My name is Benjamin Neil, a polyglot engineer in Colorado. I have had the privilege to work the past eleven years making websites, services, documentation and tools for amazing companies.
I&amp;rsquo;m obsessed with technology and programming - mainy linux, hypervisors, containers, unikernels, scala, rust, go etc. Ive got a real problem researching tools and enjoy writing then rewriting internal documentation.
Publications Recently (well in 2016) I co-authored a book called Professional Scala, it was an exciting experience and I really enjoyed the feedback from the scala community.</description></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>https://bneil.me/contact/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bneil.me/contact/</guid><description>Have questions or want to discuss programming?
if you have keybase you can follow me and im usually on the messaging app reach out on Twitter</description></item><item><title>Resume</title><link>https://bneil.me/resume/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bneil.me/resume/</guid><description>Technical Overview I really use a lot of tech soup - so these change all the time
Docker EE and Kubernetes Go, Rust, Scala and more Drone, Jenkins and Gitlab PostgreSQL, MySQL, Redis and more Vue.js, next.js Experience Compliable CTO Co-Founder Sept 2020 to Present
Same role just now with a new name!
Technical Toolset Docker, Aws Stack, Go
REBRIC Chief Technical Officer Nov 2016 to Sept 2020</description></item><item><title>now</title><link>https://bneil.me/now/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bneil.me/now/</guid><description>@@@ @@@ @@@@@@ @@@ @@@ @@@ @@@@ @@@ @@@@@@@@ @@@ @@@ @@@ @@!@!@@@ @@! @@@ @@! @@! @@! !@!!@!@! !@! @!@ !@! !@! !@! @!@ !!@! @!@ !@! @!! !!@ @!@ !@! !!! !@! !!! !@! !!! !@! !!: !!! !!: !!! !!: !!: !!: :!: !:! :!: !:! :!: :!: :!: :!: :!: :!: :: :: ::::: :: :::: :: ::: ::: ::: ::: :: : : : : :: : : : ::: ::: ::: Last Updated: Oct 8, 2021</description></item><item><title>Nondistributable Artifacts</title><link>https://bneil.me/posts/docker-nondistributable-artifacts/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bneil.me/posts/docker-nondistributable-artifacts/</guid><description>The Mystery I was reading through the docker documentation for docker registry and ran into this curious idea of nondistributable artifacts and how that related to some layers that are proprietary. Which got me thinking about how I could setup my own non distributable layers.
So looking into microsoft/windowsservercore I figured since those had some foreign layers I could take a gander at what was in the manifest which made particular layers &amp;ldquo;foreign&amp;rdquo;.</description></item></channel></rss>