<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Benjamin Neil</title><link>http://bneil.me/</link><description>Recent content on Benjamin Neil</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://bneil.me/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Rebric pt1</title><link>http://bneil.me/posts/docker/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://bneil.me/posts/docker/</guid><description>The story of Rebric First and foremost we are still trying to get
Back in late 2016 an old collegue of mine hit me up on slack and wanted to chnage the landscape of HR. Given what he&amp;rsquo;d experienced with getting a new job alot of the symptoms
fuck this</description></item><item><title>Serverless Ideas</title><link>http://bneil.me/posts/docker/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://bneil.me/posts/docker/</guid><description>OpenFaas For IoT When looking over the offerings for serverless the first application comes to mind - simply an edge for IoT. While working over the past year we&amp;rsquo;ve had I</description></item><item><title>Nondistributable Artifacts</title><link>http://bneil.me/posts/docker-nondistributable-artifacts/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://bneil.me/posts/docker-nondistributable-artifacts/</guid><description>The Mystery I was reading through the docker documentation for docker registry and ran into this curious idea of nondistributable artifacts and how that related to some layers that are proprietary. Which got me thinking about how I could setup my own non distributable layers.
So looking into microsoft/windowsservercore I figured since those had some foreign layers I could take a gander at what was in the manifest which made particular layers &amp;ldquo;foreign&amp;rdquo;.</description></item><item><title/><link>http://bneil.me/resume/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://bneil.me/resume/</guid><description>A. B. C. Always Be Coding Technical Overview Docker EE and Kubernetes Go, Rust, Scala and more Drone, Jenkins and Gitlab PostgreSQL, MySQL, Redis and more Vue.js, next.js Experience REBRIC Senior Consultant Nov 2016 to present Working as a consultant to help companies modernize their architecture which includes evangelizing kubernetes, docker swarm mode, jenkins and general civil discourse Contributed to a large shared groovy pipeline Cordinated host upgrades within a very structured entrprise environment Mentored and held brown bag session on containerization technology Proposed, designed and implemented a realtime deployment tracker used by XLR Created a custom alarm dashboard for quick diagnose of microservice issues Technical Toolset Docker, Jenkins, Bitbucket, Go</description></item><item><title>About Me</title><link>http://bneil.me/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://bneil.me/about/</guid><description>My name is Benjamin Neil, a polyglot engineer in Colorado. I have had the privilege to work the past eleven years making websites, services, documentation and tools for amazing companies.
I&amp;rsquo;m obsessed with technology and programming - mainy linux, hypervisors, containers, unikernels, scala, rust, go etc. Ive got a real problem researching tools and enjoy writing then rewriting internal documentation.
Publications Recently (well in 2016) I co-authored a book called Professional Scala, it was an exciting experience and I really enjoyed the feedback from the scala community.</description></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>http://bneil.me/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://bneil.me/contact/</guid><description>Have questions or want to discuss programming?
if you have keybase you can follow me and im usually on the messaging app reach out on Twitter</description></item></channel></rss>