<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Benjamin Neil</title><link>/</link><description>Recent content on Benjamin Neil</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Apr 2021 16:27:57 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Testing</title><link>/post/2021-04-19-taking-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Apr 2021 16:27:57 -0600</pubDate><guid>/post/2021-04-19-taking-notes/</guid><description>Hugo for note taking I&amp;rsquo;m wondering if using Hugo for writing notes would even be applicable to my current work flows. Right now I usually just use Evernote, but then I never really go into Evernote and re-review all the things ive noted.</description></item><item><title>WASM and Webmentions</title><link>/post/wasm/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2021 15:36:52 -0600</pubDate><guid>/post/wasm/</guid><description>Webmentions So as I journey through the fun webmentions, it looks like since im just using github pages, I would migrate over to using cloudflare so I could play more with webworkers. My last attempt was that Danny Devito Quote generator that I believe was working fairly well.
Although, having said that it really isnt at the point id like it to be. I originally wanted an &amp;ldquo;always sunny in philadelphia&amp;rdquo; to regale my coworkers with.</description></item><item><title>Not dead</title><link>/post/awake/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Apr 2021 11:23:39 -0600</pubDate><guid>/post/awake/</guid><description>Whats going on? It all started with finding a webring. I hadnt seen one since the mid 90&amp;rsquo;s and the accidental stumbling upon one was almost magical. If you&amp;rsquo;ve never had the pleasure, a web ring was this piece of tech that was largely social. It was a way of finding genres of websites you were interested in and daisy chaining between them. Largely this was before google owned search and the &amp;lsquo;little&amp;rsquo; guys like alta vista were king.</description></item><item><title>Nondistributable Artifacts</title><link>/post/docker-nondistributable-artifacts/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/post/docker-nondistributable-artifacts/</guid><description>The Mystery I was reading through the docker documentation for docker registry and ran into this curious idea of nondistributable artifacts and how that related to some layers that are proprietary. Which got me thinking about how I could setup my own non distributable layers.
So looking into microsoft/windowsservercore I figured since those had some foreign layers I could take a gander at what was in the manifest which made particular layers &amp;ldquo;foreign&amp;rdquo;.</description></item><item><title/><link>/resume/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/resume/</guid><description>This is what ive been up to Technical Overview Docker EE and Kubernetes Go, Rust, Scala and more Drone, Jenkins and Gitlab PostgreSQL, MySQL, Redis and more Vue.js, next.js Experience REBRIC CTO Co-Founder Nov 2016 to Present Worked in creating a platform from the ground up for a number of pivotes Manage a team of highly impressive engineers Engage daily in coffee drinking and long stares at the monitor Helped drive growth through a pandemic to a startup Technical Toolset Docker, Aws Stack, Go</description></item><item><title>About Me</title><link>/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/about/</guid><description>My name is Benjamin Neil, a polyglot engineer in Colorado. I have had the privilege to work the past eleven years making websites, services, documentation and tools for amazing companies.
I&amp;rsquo;m obsessed with technology and programming - mainy linux, hypervisors, containers, unikernels, scala, rust, go etc. Ive got a real problem researching tools and enjoy writing then rewriting internal documentation.
Publications Recently (well in 2016) I co-authored a book called Professional Scala, it was an exciting experience and I really enjoyed the feedback from the scala community.</description></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/contact/</guid><description>Have questions or want to discuss programming?
if you have keybase you can follow me and im usually on the messaging app reach out on Twitter</description></item><item><title>now</title><link>/now/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/now/</guid><description>WIP</description></item></channel></rss>