<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Benjamin Neil</title><link>/post/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Benjamin Neil</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 20:06:34 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Nextjs Crud :: Setup</title><link>/post/2021-04-21-nextjs-crud/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 20:06:34 -0600</pubDate><guid>/post/2021-04-21-nextjs-crud/</guid><description>Setup So the gist of the below is that we are creating a starter nextjs application, typescript, converting to yarn and finally installing both tailwind css and tailwind jit.
λ&amp;gt; npx create-next-app nextjs-crud --use-npm --example &amp;#34;https://github.com/vercel/next-learn-starter/tree/master/learn-starter&amp;#34; λ&amp;gt; cd nextjs-crud λ&amp;gt; touch tsconfig.json λ&amp;gt; npm install --save-dev typescript @types/react λ&amp;gt; rm -f package-lock.json λ&amp;gt; yarn add -d tailwindcss@latest postcss@latest autoprefixer@latest λ&amp;gt; npx tailwindcss init -p λ&amp;gt; yarn add @tailwindcss/jit tailwindcss postcss if you want to learn more about the &amp;lsquo;why&amp;rsquo; you should use the jit instead of using tailwind directly,</description></item><item><title>Migrating to Dynamo</title><link>/post/2021-04-20-dynamo_struct/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 10:15:26 -0600</pubDate><guid>/post/2021-04-20-dynamo_struct/</guid><description>Another store getting migrated Today&amp;rsquo;s pivotal tasks are all related towards moving things away from redis and into dynamo. So far ive gotten the underpinnings done by creating a dynamo store
The main struct looks like this
type DynamoStore struct { tableName string primaryKey string store *dynamodb.DynamoDB } The funny thing is that im basically treating dynamo in the same way I was treating redis. Which is as primarily a key value store.</description></item><item><title>On Notes</title><link>/post/2021-04-19-taking-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Apr 2021 16:27:57 -0600</pubDate><guid>/post/2021-04-19-taking-notes/</guid><description>Hugo for note taking I&amp;rsquo;m wondering if using Hugo for writing notes would even be applicable to my current work flows. Right now I usually just use Evernote, but then I never really go into Evernote and re-review all the things ive noted.
I keep feeling like there has to be a way to manage GTD, alongside tools that im working with daily because seriously, the amount of context switching in terms of apps/sites to plan any one project seems crazy.</description></item><item><title>WASM and Webmentions</title><link>/post/wasm/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2021 15:36:52 -0600</pubDate><guid>/post/wasm/</guid><description>Webmentions So as I journey through the fun webmentions, it looks like since im just using github pages, I would migrate over to using cloudflare so I could play more with webworkers. My last attempt was that Danny Devito Quote generator that I believe was working fairly well.
Although, having said that it really isnt at the point id like it to be. I originally wanted an &amp;ldquo;always sunny in philadelphia&amp;rdquo; to regale my coworkers with.</description></item><item><title>Not dead</title><link>/post/awake/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Apr 2021 11:23:39 -0600</pubDate><guid>/post/awake/</guid><description>Whats going on? It all started with finding a webring. I hadnt seen one since the mid 90&amp;rsquo;s and the accidental stumbling upon one was almost magical. If you&amp;rsquo;ve never had the pleasure, a web ring was this piece of tech that was largely social. It was a way of finding genres of websites you were interested in and daisy chaining between them. Largely this was before google owned search and the &amp;lsquo;little&amp;rsquo; guys like alta vista were king.</description></item><item><title>Nondistributable Artifacts</title><link>/post/docker-nondistributable-artifacts/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/post/docker-nondistributable-artifacts/</guid><description>The Mystery I was reading through the docker documentation for docker registry and ran into this curious idea of nondistributable artifacts and how that related to some layers that are proprietary. Which got me thinking about how I could setup my own non distributable layers.
So looking into microsoft/windowsservercore I figured since those had some foreign layers I could take a gander at what was in the manifest which made particular layers &amp;ldquo;foreign&amp;rdquo;.</description></item></channel></rss>