<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>coding on Benjamin Neil</title><link>/categories/coding/</link><description>Recent content in coding on Benjamin Neil</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 17:03:50 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/categories/coding/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Connecting/Migrations in RDS</title><link>/post/note_connecting_to_rds/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 17:03:50 -0600</pubDate><guid>/post/note_connecting_to_rds/</guid><description>Goose Since goose uses pq under the hood, to hit remote urls
goose postgres &amp;#34;user=postgres password=${PROD_PGPASS} dbname=test sslmode=disable host=database.rds.amazonaws.com&amp;#34; status PSQL / RDS I didnt have a default database created, so I needed to psql into it - summoning psql via docker container
docker run -it --rm jbergknoff/postgresql-client postgresql://postgres:${PROD_PGPASS}@database.rds.amazonaws.com:5432</description></item><item><title>Note taking apps</title><link>/post/2021-05-28_note-taking-apps/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 May 2021 18:13:24 -0600</pubDate><guid>/post/2021-05-28_note-taking-apps/</guid><description>Obsidian Currently Using
WIP</description></item><item><title>Audit Service - RDS</title><link>/post/2021-05-28_rds-audit-service/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 May 2021 11:39:43 -0600</pubDate><guid>/post/2021-05-28_rds-audit-service/</guid><description>Audit Service or Round 2 Fight Description When I started to think more critically about how interactions would work inside dynamodb for auditing I quickly learned about pain. Lots and lots of pain. Including the fact id probably end up having to use dynamodb streams and couple that with elasticsearch. So im not going to even entertain that idea and am going down the ol trusty sql route.
Creating the database Im still on an older version of terraform, so public shamming for being on 0.</description></item><item><title>Audit Service - Dynamodb</title><link>/post/audit-dynamodb/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 May 2021 11:13:53 -0600</pubDate><guid>/post/audit-dynamodb/</guid><description>Audit Service Description Decided that I wanted an audit db and service to help keep track of user behaviors. Since I already have some in Redis, and some in Postgres I thought this might be a useful exercise. The main thing id like to accomplish with this code is going to be a way to track events and break them down by week/month/year per user and per company.
Im having some self debate about creating tables for the tallies or if I should just be creating them on the fly using a query.</description></item></channel></rss>