<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>book on bneil.me</title><link>https://bneil.me/tags/book/</link><description>Recent content in book on bneil.me</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>© bneil</copyright><lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2021 13:48:53 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://bneil.me/tags/book/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Nemesis Games</title><link>https://bneil.me/review/books/nemesis_games/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2021 13:48:53 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://bneil.me/review/books/nemesis_games/</guid><description>Never break the party It&amp;rsquo;s been really interesting in other expanse novels, the close releationships. The comradery. Then here, you see people. People that want to reconnect.
It was, at this point, my investiment into the crew of the Rocinate was tested. I didn&amp;rsquo;t want these characters to leave. To explore their own backstories. But they did.
Then rocks fell and all shit went haywire. It was glorius.
Naomi&amp;rsquo;s character ark in particular was so spectacular that I had on occasion just had to stop gushing.</description></item><item><title>Cibola Burn</title><link>https://bneil.me/review/books/cibola_burn/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2021 13:48:53 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://bneil.me/review/books/cibola_burn/</guid><description>He reaches out Sometimes I read a book and I start laughing at just how bad things keep getting regardless of the beste intentions of the characters in the book. Having now gone through a few of these expanse books, I knew that the crew of the Rocinante, were going to see wild things in the through the gates. But I couldn&amp;rsquo;t even imagine how entertaining the middle of this book would be.</description></item><item><title>Abaddons Gate</title><link>https://bneil.me/review/books/abaddons_gate/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 19:22:33 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://bneil.me/review/books/abaddons_gate/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m burning through these books and this one was no different.
Maybe it&amp;rsquo;s the instant draw.
To characters whose only hope of kindling a romantic hookup is belting themselves into a junker spaceship and hurling themselves through a gate built from the reconstituted remains of Venus.
But damn.
The flair seems so human, I could see it being real.
Abaddons Gate centers around the aforementioned ring. It&amp;rsquo;s existence bringing the whole of humanity towards it.</description></item><item><title>Calibans War</title><link>https://bneil.me/review/books/calibans_war/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jun 2021 10:33:49 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://bneil.me/review/books/calibans_war/</guid><description>I couldn&amp;rsquo;t put this title down from page one. Where in Leviathans Wake I was impressed by the world building and just wild adventure, in caliban&amp;rsquo;s war the character and story arcs are on a completely different level. From a war breaking out in the solar systems only bread basket too running full throttle towards a space mutant and even a kidnapping - I was absolutely delighted.
All while introducing characters like Avasarala, a head strong - tactical politician boss bitch archetype and Bobby a gunnery sergeant who&amp;rsquo;s mental health is threatened very early in the book.</description></item><item><title>Leviathan Wakes</title><link>https://bneil.me/review/books/leviathan_wakes/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jun 2021 10:33:49 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://bneil.me/review/books/leviathan_wakes/</guid><description>Really great world building, interesting plot and just enough tension to really feel like an adventure. I was a little confused when reading this book at first since the prologue was really odd. That and the whiplash we get as we are first getting introduced into the world that James Corey paints for us.
For me my favorite character was Miller, and I was enjoying the tug of what felt like two protagonists in a single story.</description></item></channel></rss>